

Diego Hernandez
UX/UI Designer

**(S)** 31 31 47 98 49

diegohrnz12@gmail.com

O Tlajomulco de Zuñiga, Jalisco.

## **Soft Skills**

- · Problem Analysis
- · Teamwork.
- · Decision Making
- · Attention to Detail
- · Critical Thinking
- Feedback Receptiveness

## Certifications

User Experience (UX) Design 2023
Official Google Certification

# **Technical Skills**

- Figma
- Adobe Suite
- Sketch
- Project Management Tools
- · Wireframing Tools
- InVision

# Language

- Spanish Native
- English C1

# Linkedin profile



### About me

I am a UX/UI Designer with Front-End experience, passionate about design and the development of digital products. I have a strong background in design and am currently specializing in Web Development, with a meticulous focus on creating intuitive and engaging user experiences.

### **Education**

2023 - 2024	Oracle next education + Alura
	Web Development - Online Mode
2023 - 2024	University of Guadalajara - In Progress
	Web Development - Online Mode
2023 - 2024	Coder House - Diploma Program
	User Experience Design and Research
2023 - 2024	Google Inroads - Certification
	Certification in User Experience (UX) Design
2013 - 2018	University of Colima
	Bachelor's Degree in Design & Architecture - Graduated
2014 - 2016	University of Colima - English Language
	Foreign Language - English - Conversational C1
2015 - 2016	University of Alicante, Spain
	Bachelor's Degree in Design - Graduated

## **Experience**

## IMJ MEDIA

UX/UI Designer | October 2023 - Present

UX Designer skilled in Web Design, leveraging Agile Methodologies to ensure iterative improvement and collaboration. Experienced in UX Research to understand user needs and behaviors, and proficient in Prototyping to create intuitive, user-centered experiences that streamline the path from concept to final product

#### Coder House

Junior UX Designer -by project | September 2023 - December 2023

Project for a client by Codderhouse, incorporating agile methodologies such as Design Thinking and Scrum, applying design principles from UX research through to design and prototyping for the final digital product

### IMEC Sa de Cv

Designer | February 2019 - September 2023

In IMEC, I worked as a designer, primarily handling design tasks using software from the Adobe and Autodesk suites. I also ventured into the company's web design, applying my UX design skills to enhance user navigation

#### Freelance

UX/UI Designer |

Freelance UX designer with hands-on projects and designs for small startups, including teamwork, autonomy, Scrum methodology, and collaboration with developers.